The Anomaly is a thriller, action, science fiction film directed by Noel Clarke.
A former soldier is taken captive and awakens in the back of a van where he learns
that he only has less than 10 minutes to figure out how he got there.
Ryan Reeve, played by Noel Clarke.
Harkin, played by Ian Somerhalder.
Shanghai's friend, played by Kumud Pant.
Dana, played by Alexis Knapp.
Alex's mother, played by Victoria Broom.
Dr. Langham, played by Brian Cox.
The Anomaly is a 2014 British science fiction action film co-produced and
directed by Noel Clarke, who also starred in the lead role.
The film co-stars Ian Somerhalder and Luke Hemsworth.
The film was panned by critics.
This is Somerhalder's final acting film before his retirement in 2024.
The film explores themes of mind control, future,
technology, kidnapping, memory loss.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.